Now, Seras...
Take off your clothes.
Huh?
The people of Mils saw you
in that outfit, right?
Oh...
Sorry to give you the wrong idea.
I'll admit I was a bit shaken.
H-Hold on a moment. When did we start
acting like our agreement is still in effect?
I have a proposal for you.
Why don't you negotiate with the Witch
of Taboos and have her shelter you?
The Witch of Taboos?
No one has ever figured out
where she lives, right?
Indeed.
I'm heading to the Land of Monsters myself
to learn more about that ancient script.
So our agreement's still good, no?
Why go so far for me?
You remind me of someone.
You don't look or sound very similar,
and your personalities are different, but...
If I had to say, you have the same aura.
So cutting out on you here
would feel like abandoning my aunt.
Sir Tooka...
You truly are a kind man.
Yeah, I already know.
Not enough to level up, huh?
Now then...
If you answer our questions honestly,
I'll have mercy on you.
Damn brat! Don't think you can get away
with defying the Black Dragon Knights!
- Damn brat! Don't think you can get away
- I'm not lying.
I can dismiss the nonlethal setting
and spare him from his suffering.
Who is it that wants me dead?
A-All right.
I'm a little curious.
I wanna see how a former high elf princess
who swore her sword to the Holy Empire
reacts when she learns the truth!
Seras!
He's currently out of range.
No, worse yet, he's—
Seras Ashrain.
His garb and hair are white.
His eyes alone are a vivid red...
I am Civit,
though many in this world
call me by another name...
"Humanity's Strongest."
HUMANITY'S STRONGEST, CIVIT GARTLAND
Hand them over.
Surrender to me your nation's strongest.
Civit Gartland...
The Five Dragoons, too.
But there are only four of them.
THE FIVE DRAGOONS
BLACK DRAGON KNIGHTS
- There's one missing...
I sealed his lips, Orban.
ORBAN
- Look, was there any need to kill him?
You shouldn't get carried away
with side gigs either.
I take it Ortola ordered this?
Ah, Seras...
Everything about you restored this old,
withered ruler to
a man brimming with vigor.
I don't begrudge letting you escape.
I don't begrudge it, but...
The thought of another man
one day defiling you...
Oh, Seras!
I'll pay as much money as it takes.
And if I must offer anything else,
I will gladly do so.
So, please...
Please die and vanish from this world!
Emperor Ortola... wants me...?
Aw, now she's frozen up.
Poor thing.
Gizun was going to be a
hindrance at this stage,
therefore I killed him.
Had he dodged, however,
I would have let him live.
Gizun was paralyzed and unable to move,
but he couldn't have evaded that either way.
How should we deal with Seras Ashrain?
What did His Majesty say?
SCHWEITZ
VICE CAPTAIN OF THE BLACK DRAGON KNIGHTS
- That it was up to us.
What shall we do?
How about passing her around our subordinates
as a reward before we kill her?
That would cause issues, Schweitz.
The former holy emperor asked us to bring
her corpse back with her purity intact.
Wh-What nonsense are you people spouting?!
Apparently the geezer can't die
in peace so long as you're alive.
Y-You lie...
Seras Ashrain, I'll grant you
the right to win your life.
The right?
Sir Civit is saying that if you duel him
and win, he'll let you go, Lady Seras.
MITAMA
- The Spirit Regalia of Holy Neah's
knight captain is renowned.
The Spirit Regalia of Holy Neah's
I would be satisfied with the opportunity
to test your Spirit Regalia in battle...
Or so I thought until just moments ago.
Sir Civit?
I now find myself more interested
in this young man than Seras Ashrain.
CIVIT GARTLAND
CAPTAIN OF THE BLACK DRAGON KNIGHTS
- Who might you be?
I've got a knife to my throat...
But he's still out of range.
Humanity's Strongest...
Civit Gartland.
A man more dangerous than the Soul Eater.
Why are you grinning?
Ah, right.
Why is it that moments like this make me...
Hey, Civit Gartland.
Care to have a little chat?
I would hear your name first.
It's Hati Skoll.
I see. An alias?
Well, yeah.
So you have a need to
conceal your real name.
I take it there's some history there.
Sir Civit, why on earth are
you bothering with this boy?
Don't you find it odd?
He stands before the Five Dragoons
but he's not frightened.
He's waiting for an opening
so he can attack.
Attack you?
He knows that one wrong move
will see him instantly slaughtered.
Yet even in such a situation,
he smiles and seeks conversation.
Huh.
He's a clever man.
It's too early to close
the curtains on this stage.
Don't get hasty.
Make the wrong choices
and this is over in a flash.
I'd like to ask you something.
Very well. State your question.
I gather you're searching for a foe
who can satisfy you.
Indeed I am.
But aren't there plenty of strong, superhuman
opponents crawling around everywhere?
For example, the goddess of Alion.
My land of Bakoss and Alion
have forged close relations.
However...
I have high hopes for the heroes
she's summoned from another world.
The power of her blessing grants
such heroes the ability
to rapidly approach the peak of strength.
I have faith that they will prove worthy
foes for me, and so I await that day.
- I have faith that they will prove worthy
- He's oozing with absolute self-confidence.
His only desire is finding
and fighting powerful opponents.
"Humanity's Strongest"
is too strong for his own good.
- "Humanity's Strongest"
- Seras Ashrain.
is too strong for his own good.
- I've lost interest in you at this point.
I'll at least do you the honor
of delivering your head
to Cattleya, the princess of Neah.
You would do that to the princess?
Silence, resigned weakling!
You are the reason Bakoss
suddenly changed its stance
and invaded Neah in the
first place, Seras Ashrain.
What?!
Why are you acting surprised?
You already had an inkling
of the truth, didn't you?
Bakoss wiped out Neah because
our goddess demanded they
hand over their little paladin,
and your holy emperor refused.
They reaped what they sowed.
That can't be...
Nothing kills my interest more than those who
refuse to struggle even in the face of death.
Even if they're weak,
as long as they come at me...
Though it goes without saying that I'd greatly
prefer it if they have the power to kill me.
I've put together our path to survival now.
Civit Gartland.
You desire a foe who can
threaten your life, right?
Indeed I do.
Then how about I become that for you?
You said those the goddess blesses
rapidly approach peak strength, right?
Playing this card will
be our watershed moment.
My real identity is Touka Mimori,
a hero from another world.
Sir Tooka... you're a
hero from another world?
Now the pieces click.
That's why something felt off.
However, what are you doing
in a place like this?
Civit is capable of sensing lies,
so blatant falsehoods won't fly here.
I hold a unique position,
even among my fellow heroes.
So I'm acting alone, independent of them,
all at the goddess's behest.
None of that was untrue.
It was all fact.
But Civit can interpret it as he will.
Why are you acting independent
of the other heroes?
Apparently, I'm in an altogether
different league than the rest.
Oh?
That's right. I'm an E-Class hero.
We're not at all on the same level.
Because of that, I was sent out on my own.
A man even the goddess
recognizes as special, huh?
Yeah. Seems I'm really quite special to her.
Now this is interesting.
So, hero from another world,
what is it you'd ask of me?
Deferment.
You want me to spare you for now?
What's in it for me?
I'll grow stronger than I am now
and then kill you.
You say you'll kill me?
I'll grow stronger than
anyone or anything else.
I'm going to gain enough power
to trample that goddess!
Then let me ask you this.
How do you plan to grow so strong?
I'm headed to the Land
of Golden-Eyed Monsters.
I'm walking a different path
than the other heroes.
The Goddess Vicius
has granted me that freedom.
If they survive the ruins and reach
the surface, we interfere no more.
Alion grants that person
the right to live freely.
Either way, I plan to return to her.
So you're saying there's no
chance you'll just disappear.
No way in hell.
Indeed, I swear I'll make it back
to the goddess...
To exact my revenge!
Very well.
I wish to see this.
I want to see what becomes of your growth.
Then I'd like us to fight to the death.
Yeah, me too.
So let's settle this just between
us one day, Civit Gartland!
How delightful!
That will to fight! That hostility!
Very well! I shall let you live, Tooka Mimori!
Now that's the spirit.
You may leave this place without worry.
Once we have silenced Seras Ashrain,
then we shall leave as well.
That won't do.
I need Seras's power in order to make it
through the Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters.
You'd take her with you
without the goddess's approval?
That doesn't matter.
I'll use Seras Ashrain
to grow stronger for myself.
That's all there is to it.
Good, Tooka Mimori!
Then I suppose I shall grant
Seras Ashrain mercy as well.
Wait, what?! Civit!
Tooka says he needs her to get stronger.
We can always kill her
after his duel with me.
Yeah, but even so...
What if he disappears on you?
Silence.
Or I'll kill you!
- Sir Tooka?
- Sorry, Seras, that's how it is.
Schweitz.
Tell Grimm Ritter as well,
wherever he's off wasting time.
No one is to lay a hand on these two.
Very well.
This first act proved to be a performance
that far surpassed my imagination.
It was an excellent lead into the next.
I look forward to the day when
we meet again, Tooka Mimori!
It worked.
I managed to get Civit to let us go.
And I won my gamble!
Meaning...
He's in range now!
Para...
Tooka!
...lyze!
You bastard!
I'm impressed, "Humanity's Strongest."
Sorry, but I have no intention of dragging
things out with you for that long.
This isn't some nice little play,
Civit Gartland.
Why not? Because it's a tale of revenge.
Looking at things logically,
you Black Dragon Knights
are nothing but a liability for me.
Therefore, you must be eliminated.
There is no next act.
What... have you done, Tooka?!
Like I said, I'm putting a hard stop
to this little song and dance,
Black Dragon Knights!
Tooka...!
I told you, didn't I?
I'm in a different league.
Poison.
Tooka!
They don't call him "Humanity's
Strongest" for nothing.
This is the second time I've seen someone
force themself to move while paralyzed.
But it's just suicide.
That was close.
I've never seen anyone move so much
after eating my Paralysis and Poison combo.
I'll need to remain ready for
anything until I see him expire.
A signal to a squad
on standby elsewhere, huh?
Sir Tooka.
I'm staying here to see
the Five Dragoons dead.
You're welcome to run if you want.
I shall stay as well.
I am currently your bodyguard, after all.
Though in exchange, I will be accepting
those blue dragon gems as my reward.
Yeah, got it.
Sir Schweitz?!
Wh-What happened to you?!
- Azlan...
- S-Sir Civit!
- Y-You're actually wounded?!
- Kill them...
from the sky!
Don't get too close!
Kill them at range!
Kill those two no matter what!
We're linked.
There are two problems with this ability.
What are you doing?!
Hurry!
First is how long it takes
to enter this state.
Second is how quick it burns
through my MP while it's active.
In other words...
this power we gained from the
monster enhancement solution
is for super short combat!
We're dropping them, Piggymaru!
All right, let's settle this for good!
Assault Accel!
Paralyze!
Once we're linked, Piggymaru is half "me."
So as long as we're connected like this,
- Tooka!
- his farthest tendril
starts my effective range.
- Sleep!
- his farthest tendril
starts my effective range.
his farthest tendril
Your skill has leveled up.
INFLICT FROZEN, INFLICT DARKNESS, INFLICT RAGE
- New skills have been unlocked.
Berserk!
This new Berserk skill probably
induces violent urges.
Combined with Paralyze,
it could kill an enemy quickly.
Dismiss Paralyze and Sleep.
Dark.
Wh-What? M-My vision! I can't see!
So this one obscures their eyes with darkness?
Orban wanted to kill Seras for money.
Schweitz wanted to use her
as a plaything for his men.
So using them as lab rats...
doesn't bother me at all.
They're lowlifes, just like me.
TOOKA MIMORI
- You have leveled up.
It's quiet.
Paralyze.
Tooka...
You really are far too exceptional,
Civit Gartland.
Just who the hell are you...?
I'm nothing grand like a hero who
will save the world anymore.
Now I'm just a simple avenger.
So this is how Humanity's Strongest
meets his end, huh?
Now we should be able to cover
Seras Ashrain's tracks.
Thank you.
I'm the one who should be thanking you.
I was glad you stayed by me.
I didn't think I could let you die.
If I had let you fall here,
I felt I would never recover this time.
I must say, Sir Tooka,
you're wearing a rather gentle expression.
Maybe because I'm thinking of someone gentle.
That aunt you mentioned?
So, this Hero Slayer...
He could potentially surpass
Humanity's Strongest one day.
He's an aggressive, bloodthirsty man.
What's the matter?
The dragons that the Five Dragoons rode
were a different size than the others, right?
What? O-Oh, yes.
Then I think... I already crushed him.
Huh?
You were even able to defeat
the Hero Slayer so easily?
Apparently.
TITLE: S-CLASS HERO
AYAKA SOGOU
- I still haven't awakened a unique skill?
I still haven't awakened a unique skill?
Huh? What's with this chick?
NYANTAN KIKIPAT
FOLLOWER OF VICIUS
- I'm here on behalf of the Goddess Vicius.
I'm here on behalf of the Goddess Vicius.
Henceforth, when she is preoccupied, I shall—
A skinny shrimp like you
is gonna boss us around?
I mean, are you any stronger than we are?
You must be Oyamada.
Your foul mouth is indeed
enough to furrow one's brow.
Would you care to find out?
What?
Damn... it...
I don't believe it!
How can she be so fast?
I hope that will suffice as an introduction.
We're returning to the royal capital.
You all are to enter the next stage soon.
I see.
Nothing to be proud of, you see.
Still, I'll use my judgment and mercilessly
trample any obstacle to my revenge.
I can't say I don't have my own thoughts
and feelings about the goddess of Alion now.
So please make good use of my strength
in the name of your revenge.
This is just a selfish quest for vengeance.
I hardly see any of the righteousness
or honor and conviction
that you value in it.
No, you risked your life without any regard
for the dangers involved in order to save me.
I want to repay that debt.
As long as you believe it is right,
I will happily accept any treatment.
If you're that insistent,
then do as you please.
Thank you very much.
Can I rely on your strength, Seras Ashrain?
I promise to live up to your expectations.
I'm sorry, Seras.
Sir Tooka?
I plan to return the favor
to you one day as well.
I always repay my debts,
be it out of gratitude...
or out of spite.
Good work today.
I knew I was right to ask you
to watch over the heroes.
You're strong, and you're wise.
And above all, you're loyal.
Isn't that right, Nyantan?
Yes.
My, my, what's the matter?
It feels like your mouth isn't moving.
Thank you very much for the
unchanging display of loyalty.
The day the heroes clash with the
forces of the Great Demon Empire
might be getting surprisingly close.
MONROY'S BLOODSPORT CHAMPION